<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Anbuselvan Palaniyandi</title><link>https://anbuchelva.in/categories/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Anbuselvan Palaniyandi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anbuchelva.in/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Collect Ather Ride Logs using API</title><link>https://anbuchelva.in/posts/appscript/collect-ather-logs-using-api/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://anbuchelva.in/posts/appscript/collect-ather-logs-using-api/</guid><description>&lt;p>It has been 6+ months since the OCR based telegram bot was setup and opened to users. There were 60+ users using the bot and few setup their own bot at a time and the count started reducing to single digit. I expected that as long as there in any interactions from users, it will not work out.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I started setting up the API based bot 3+ months go and showed how to setup their own in the telegram group. Some are using it and found it is useful.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I want to write a proper document how to set it up so that it would be easy to implement. This bot will not be available centrally as it contains lot of personal information and holds lot of data which doesn&amp;rsquo;t handle the free usage provided by Google and Telegram as highlighted in the previous post. So, if you plan to use it, you need to get your hands dirty.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The OCR based bot is continue to exist, there&amp;rsquo;s no change on that.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Collect Ather Logs in Google Sheets via Telegram Bot</title><link>https://anbuchelva.in/posts/appscript/collect-ather-logs-to-google-sheets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://anbuchelva.in/posts/appscript/collect-ather-logs-to-google-sheets/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have been using the Ather 450X for over 8 months now. I prefer driving this vehicle more compared to my previous ones.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Ather app provides statistics such as the last 20 rides, monthly ride logs, charging statistics, etc. However, they recently stopped sending monthly logs. To continue analyzing the data, I decided to collect the logs myself.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>